hello hello everybody
before I start I just want to say to
everyone up here
you're welcome
in the other place but Hollywood could
these 10 people make the kind of money
they make
and sleep with the kind of people they
sleep with
[Applause]
you too Ron Burgundy
[Music]
[Applause]
foreign
listen people listen listen I don't have
a lot of time all right
[Applause]
I don't have a lot of time I'm
I'm currently
I'm currently over at stage 24.
hosting Spike TVs your mother's a fat
award show
[Applause]
some real clever writing great energy
over there
boy we got a great gang of talented
Comics here tonight we've got a Tom
Dreesen uh
Willie Tyler and Lester I didn't
realize Lester was a live human being
Aaron mule deer
Fanny flag top notch
[Applause]
star-studded evening
listen I'm just gonna cut to the chase
Justin Bieber Justin Bieber
you've been taking it on the chin
tonight you really have in fact
absolutely abused
and I'm just here to say one thing
you people don't know what the hell
you're talking about as far as I'm
concerned this guy is doing it right
here's a couple things I know
September 1st 2014 Bieber arrested for a
collision with a minivan in his hometown
of Stratford Ontario Canada
and then beat up the occupant of the
minivan nice work
October 18 2010 Bieber accused of
assaulting a 12-year-old at a laser tag
arena kaboom
[Applause]
I only wish the kid was a nine-year-old
foreign
[Applause]
2013 Bieber flies into Munich with his
pet monkey Mali
doesn't have the proper paperwork
so he leaves it at a zoo
in Germany
it's a monkey
it's named Mali
don't think twice you leave it at a
German Zoo
March 4th 2013 two hours late to a
concert in Dubai because he refused to
stop playing a video game save what
talked to loogie at his neighbor after
the guy complained that Bieber was
driving 100 miles per hour in his gated
community neighborhood eat that
July 10 2013 Bieber pees in a restaurant
mop bucket
as he runs off he sprays a photograph of
Bill Clinton with a bottle of blue
liquid and yells Bill Clinton
who hasn't done that you hypocritical
this kid has spunk
Moxie and probably a few other STDs okay
[Applause]
I've always encouraged people to Stay
classy
and what's more classy than hanging out
with Floyd Mayweather
would I love to see beams spending time
with Oscar Pistorius of course I would
but that day will come
foreign
people refer to Mr Bieber as a as a kid
or a boy
but here's a news flash gang he's a man
a full-grown man who works and loves
and makes things with his hands
a man who sings songs for nine-year-olds
and cuts his hair like a gay figure
skater
[Applause]
this guy just continues to impress is
there anything he can't do
in fact I pulled my my pants down
and took a big creamy in the green
room because I thought to myself that's
how the Biebs would do it
again and again and again
if anything Justin Bieber
not only do you need to continue to live
your life with the same Reckless abandon
I suggest you turn up the heat
yeah
oh
and one last thing
if you're watching from your monkey cage
in Germany
go to bed Mally good night
[Applause]
you know Jeff a lot of your friends
wanted to be here but couldn't make it
fortunately we were able to send a video
crew down to a very special friend
someone who is very close to our guest
of honor please welcome Jeff Foxworthy's
cow
to suck my dick
I got a peek for a drummer because
they're one of the smartest mammals just
below the dolphin and just above Larry
the Cable Guy
Jeff is an original thinker for instance
most people use their hands to milk a
cow not Jeff he uses his mouth so that
his hands are free to play with my ass
thank you
I've got E coli cells on my tits that
are funnier than this guy
Jeff's hacked my he's funnier
darker and better constructive
you say I think I can get a
development deal for at the WB
please welcome a very special guest
foreign
[Music]
[Applause]
thank you very much I appreciate that
introduction
thank you thank you
it's an honor to be here tonight
it's always good to be in Manhattan
[Applause]
Manhattan as I understand is an island
[Music]
[Applause]
an island entirely surrounded by water
thank you
I want to thank Comedy Central for
[Applause]
long made this opportunity to be at The
Jeff Foxworthy roast
I like Jeff
foreign
it's my favorite comedian
[Applause]
I like his jokes
they're simple
Jeff is a simple man
he's a simple man
but he is a smart man
now he doesn't like to show it because
when he does folks start talking to him
real fast
I understand that
I can identify
I know a lot of folks joke about me
a lot of people say I'm not the
brightest bulb in a knife drawer
I followed Jeff's career
he was destined to be a comedian
his grandfather was funny
his father was funny
just funny
tree don't fall far from the nuts
Jeff and I have something in common as I
look around the room I can see that he
surrounds himself with a lot of
successful people
and I've done the same
my cabinet is filled with Sterling men
and women
I've got a secretary of defense Donald
rumpelstiltskins
I'm also proud of my Vice President Dick
Cheney I appreciate him I uh
just wish I knew where he was
foreign
office I just walk out into the hallway
and you know Marco
I care about this country
I care about the people of this country
I care about our senior citizens
I'll tell you something
older citizens face the highest risk of
death in this country
seniors die every day
I care about our economy
I'm asked every day Mr President what
about our deficit
what about our Mountain deficit
what are you going to do
I understand these concerns
and I share these concerns
and that is why today
I have but before I have put before
Congress
[Applause]
a proposal
to sell Canada
finally let me say this
everybody else tonight's been
uh
ripping on you
laughs
I want to say a word of encouragement
I appreciate Jeff Foxworth I appreciate
his uh
I appreciate his good family values
I appreciate the fact he's not only a
family man but he's religious man he
doesn't want it
but Jeff is an example that religion
doesn't have to divide us
it doesn't have to tear us apart
it can bring us together
and so I guess here look here here's a
visual look at here
okay
you see her look here there's the church
nurse statement
open the door look at all the paper
all right
thank you
God bless you Jeff God bless you all and
God bless America thank you very much
thank you
foreign
he's a legend the executive who brought
Full House to network television
Soul Schwartz
[Applause]
[Music]
I remember
the day that uh uh they came to me with
the Full House pitch
it was the last day my assistant
Jacqueline blew me I remember it clearly
and in walked in the Full House people
and they pitched their little show their
dream show their classic and I said it's
a yes but I wanted to Star three
Schmucks I've never heard of
because I want to prove that time slot
is everything
foreign
let me tell you something
John Stamos you are the most talented
actor that I have ever come across you
are wonderful you're delightful you're a
dream you're fantastic
no one has ever touched your talent it
is remarkable you are the best performer
I have ever seen my balls are clapping
you are truly God's favorite actor John
Stamos
uh oh by the way I've already read
tomorrow's variety I get it early you've
been replaced on ER by Jerry O'Connell
[Applause]
true Mensch my pride and joy who I
discovered 25 years ago Bob Saget I'm
not yes
I think you're more than just the sitcom
dad or the guy who hosts that video show
you're really one of the shittiest
Comics I've ever seen
the other day I'd after all these years
I'd never met the Olsen twins he
introduced me to them I said Tim how do
I tell them apart he says Ashley
swallows
what's my character's name again
Sal Schwartz Bob he called him Saul she
demos are so not Jewish please welcome
Saul Schwartz
[Applause]
the truth is Bob we've worked together
for many many years and I'm starting to
think I have Alzheimer's because I can't
remember a single funny thing you ever
said
all right I'm not around
I said to them before the show I said uh
I want to say something nice about him
now and I swear on the screen it's a
sincere moment
what a sincere moment no what I want to
say to you is we never hang out I'd like
to
we uh we see each other we're always
happy to see each other I've always
liked you and uh I remember when we
first met you asked me if I knew how dry
my grandma's vagina was those are the
first thing I was opening for you in the
80s and uh that's the first thing you
said to me and I knew that I liked you
from that moment on
isn't that a fantastic you never met
somebody hey how do you know how to try
[Applause]
a great person
but I think the world of you and for me
it was an honor to be here tonight
thanks
[Applause]
we are very excited and I'm just going
to say an honor to introduce our next
roaster he's responsible not just for my
career but for every single person's
career in this entire room ladies and
Gentlemen please welcome the president
of Hollywood
foreign
[Applause]
[Music]
hello hello everybody
before I start I just want to say to
everyone up here
you're welcome
no other place but Hollywood could these
10 people make the kind of money they
make
and sleep with the kind of people they
sleep with
Seth Rogen
[Laughter]
you're welcome you Harry Canuck
I Hollywood made the world accept you
I put you on a movie poster and I said
deal with it
and then I put Barbra Streisand on that
poster and the world said no
The Guilt Trip
listen if I wanted to watch two ugly
Jews weaving through traffic I'd watch
Seinfeld's web series
all right
Joan I'm assuming you're here because
Seth is
people call me all the time and they say
Hollywood do we really need two of these
guys
but I owe you Jonah I own you
if I try to buy you an iTunes it would
say are you sure you want to purchase
because you already own this
[Applause]
Eddie Sandberg
the correct pronunciation
looking forward to your new show
Brooklyn Nine-Nine
funny cops
you're always pushing the envelope
[Applause]
it seems like graffiti and pickpockets
can't wait to see episode 10 when
Brooklyn Nine-Nine as they deal with a
rape
oh I dropped the rape kit smorgy door
that's gonna be fun
disease you're welcome
Aziz I am my how you've never taken the
stereotypical Indian Rose
I just want to tell you that if you did
you would make so much more money
[Applause]
if you came out here right now but
crossed eyes playing a sitar I would
fall on my ass laughing
foreign
but still what an actor
such phenomenal range
you're like the Daniel Day-Lewis of only
doing one thing
[Music]
[Applause]